感觉没多久之前
It feels like it wasn't that long ago
我们才来这里为哈雷做产检啊
we were here doing this for Halley.
因为真的没多久
'Cause it wasn't.
感谢你提醒我  在我们走之前
Which reminds me, before we leave,
先把你结扎了
let's get you a vasectomy.
真有心  但今天你才是主角
Oh, that's sweet, but today is all about you.
你们俩准备好知道孩子的性别了吗
So, you two ready to find out the sex of this baby?
-是的  -当然
- Yeah. - Absolutely.
哈雷是想要个弟弟还是妹妹呢
Is Halley hoping for a little brother or a little sister?
她才九个月大
Well, she's nine months old,
只对会丁当响  或我胸罩里的玩意感兴趣
so unless it jingles or is in my bra, she doesn't care.
那你们俩呢
And how about you two?
第一胎的时候  我们很想要个女孩
You know, for the first one, we really wanted a girl,
但这一次  我们无所谓了
but this time around, we don't have a preference.
是啊  男孩女孩  只要健康就好
Yeah. Boy, girl, as long as it's healthy.
是个男孩
Well, it's a boy.
不是吧  你们不是真的失望吧
Come on, you can't really be disappointed.
我自己都当不好一个男人了
Hey, I barely know how to be a man myself.
现在还得教别人吗
Now I have to teach someone?
常言道"没能力的  就去教人"
As the saying goes, those who can't do, teach.
你不想要个孩子版的霍华德吗
Don't you want a little version of Howard?
我已经有个孩子版的霍华德了
I already have a little version of Howard.
我现在要有儿子了
Now I'm having a son?
我得教他各种体育运动
I'll have to teach him how to play sports,
还得带他看体育比赛
and-and watch sports
然后...  然后...  然后...
and-and-and-and-and-and...
他碰到瓶颈  想不出还有什么爷们的事了
He just ran out of man things. He's in trouble.
没事啊  我们都会帮忙你
It's okay. We're all here to help.
对啊  这孩子会有许多很爷们的榜样
Yes. And this baby will have plenty of manly role models.
我很确定伯纳黛特教不了他的东西
Now, I'm certain that whatever Bernadette can't teach him,
佩妮能教
Penny can.
她能尿进瓶子里呢
Uh, she can pee into a bottle.
只要瓶口大过硬币就行
Anything with a neck wider than a nickel.
华仔  你有很多能教我们孩子的事情啊
Howie, there's a lot of amazing things you can teach a son.
对啊  比如你总是能选出最合适的抑酸剂
Yeah. You do always know how to pick just the right antacid.
我不知道这个能否传承
I don't know if I can teach that.
这是我与生俱来的天赋
It's just something I was born with.
打起精神来嘛  你还会造东西啊
Come on. You can build things.
你还曾是个宇航员
You were an astronaut.
这倒是
That's true.
我小时候就曾经搭过火箭模型
You know, as a kid, I used to make model rockets.
估计跟儿子一起搭还挺不错
That'd be pretty cool to do with a son.
火箭模型  终于聊到点有意思的了
Model rockets. Finally, something interesting.
你倾向用何种方式回收火箭呢
What is your preferred mode of recovery?
谢尔顿   现在是在帮忙我们的朋友
Sheldon, we're helping our friends.
然后聊到了火箭模型不是吗
And we got to model rockets, yeah?
虽然路程索然无味  但皇天不负有心人
It was a tedious road, but well worth the effort.
-你们帮他想好名字了吗  -艾米
- So, have you thought of any names? - Amy.
我们终于聊到了火箭模型
We finally got to model rockets.
你干嘛把话题又转回去
Why are you turning back?
第十一季  第四集
你要去哪里
Hey, where are you going?
回去干洗店  你看这个
Back to the dry cleaner. Look at this.
我星际舰队的制服没洗干净
They didn't get the stain out of my Starfleet uniform.
影集《星际迷航》中星际联邦的正规军队及外太空探索部队
要不是你整天让我涂绿漆再穿它跟你上床
Well, if you didn't make me wear the green body paint in bed,
你也不用常常拿去让人干洗了
you wouldn't have to get it dry-cleaned so much.
没事  值得
Nah, it's worth it.
等等  是你妈妈打来
Hey, wait, it's your mom.
太遗憾  她错过我了
Oh, too bad. She just missed me!
你好啊  贝弗利
Hey, Beverly.
你好啊  佩妮
Oh, hello, Penny.
莱纳德刚走
Uh, Leonard just left.
他要知道错过了你电话  一定会很难过
He's gonna be so upset he mssed your call.
怎么会
Why?
因为他...
Because he...
我也不知道
Yeah, I don't know.
你最近好吗
How are you?
你是指个人方面还是工作上
Did you mean personally or professionally?
个人方面
Um, personally?
比如你昨晚干嘛了
Like, what'd you do last night?
我去了一个男人家  跟他吃了古巴菜
I had Cuban food at the home of a man
但跟他的性爱却令我十分不满
with whom I shared unsatisfying intercourse.
好吧
Wow. Okay.
我掐指一算你的下一个问题
And to anticipate your next questions,
答案是烤猪肉与侧身传教士式
roasted pork and sideways missionary.
当然  不意外  毕竟你们吃很饱
Sure. Sure. 'Cause you were full.
我多少年没看过这些东西了
I haven't looked at all this stuff in years.
我也有
Had it.
我家车库烧了全靠它
Burnt down my garage with it.
我小时候有过三个火箭模型
I had three model rockets as a kid,
那是印度最大的三个太空计划了
and that was the largest space program in India.
你居然有土星五号火箭的模型吗
You have a replica Saturn V?
对啊  我爸在他...  你懂的
Yeah. My dad bought it before he, you know,
抛妻弃子前买给我的
abandoned our family.
你可真幸福
Lucky duck.
一直不想在没有他的情况下拆开
Could never bring myself to open it without him.
真傻
It's silly.
一点都不傻啊
No, it's not silly.
我也一直想要我爸爸跟我一起做火箭模型
I always wanted my dad to build rockets with me,
可是他没兴趣
but he wasn't interested.
是啊  令人失望的父亲们
Ah, yes, disappointing fathers.
我也有同感
Tell me about it.
我还记得我16岁生日  我爸给我买了奔驰
I remember for my 16th birthday, my dad bought me a Mercedes.
那种小台  入门款的奔驰而已
Like, a little one, like a starter Mercedes.
他前脚刚把车钥匙给我
He had barely handed me the keys
后脚就得赶去上班
before he had to rush back to work.
我就再也没见过他...
I didn't see him again till, like,
那天一直到深夜他才回来
pretty late that night.
言归正传
Anyway...
虽然我对他的离去还有怨气
...as angry as I was with him leaving,
但我大概就是因为搭过这些模型
building this stuff is probably what led me
才去当了工程师
to become an engineer.
我想我爸爸也是
I suppose, in his own way,
用了他自己的方法鼓励我追求科学
my dad also encouraged me to pursue science.
比如就是他教了我
I mean, he is the one that taught me
原来屁是可燃的
that flatulence is combustible.
还有  涤纶运动短裤不会烧起来
And also, polyester gym shorts don't burn.
而是会融化
They melt.
是啊  我想我会成为天体物理学家
Yeah, I guess I'm an astrophysicist because,
也是因为小时候  我说我想看星星
as a kid, I said I like to look at the stars,
夏威夷凯克天文台的凯克望远镜是世界上口径第二大的光学/近红外线望远镜
所以我爸送我去夏威夷参观凯克望远镜
so my dad sent me to Hawaii to visit the Keck telescope.
去你们的  哥的苦你们不懂
Screw you. My pain is real.
其实呢  忘了那些往事吧
You know what? Forget the past.
我们俩一起来搭这个火箭模型如何
What do you say you and me build this rocket?
感觉会成为我们俩真正交心的一次机会
That sounds like it could be a real bonding experience for us.
对吧
Right?
我懂了
Oh, I see.
你觉得这是一件好事
Oh, you think that's a positive.
所以你不想跟谢尔顿与霍华德玩了吗
So, you don't want to hang out with Sheldon and Howard?
他们因为可怜的童年而聊得来
No, they were bonding over their sad childhoods,
而我的臭爸妈却从小在我身旁支持我
and my stupid parents were always there for me.
这些是什么
What's all this?
我在把哈雷穿不下的衣服装箱收起来
I'm just boxing up all the clothes Halley's outgrown.
以后估计是用不到了
Guess we won't need them anymore.
别着急
Oh, well, slow down.
里面有一部分男孩也能穿的吧
I'm sure there's some you could reuse for a boy.
爸爸的小女孩吗
Daddy's little girl?
好吧  但如果我们把他改成...
Okay, well, what if we, uh, change it to say,
爸爸的小女孩杀手
Daddy's little girl magnet?
你看  小帅哥就能穿啦
Boom! Boy shirt.
这件呢
What about this?
好吧
Uh, okay.
把裙子部分去掉  在前胸加个闪电的符号
Uh, pull off the skirt, slap a lightning bolt on the front,
就成了闪电侠宝宝
and you got baby Flash.
在底下加长袖
Stick a long sleeve under it.
你看  就成了谢尔顿宝宝
Boom! Baby Sheldon.
你很在行嘛
Wow, you're really good at this.
拜托
Oh, please.
我也不是第一次把女娃装改成男娃装了
This isn't my first time turning girl clothes into boy clothes.
怎么  你小时候也穿过姐姐的二手衣吗
Why? You got your sister's hand-me-downs?
就当是吧
Yeah, that.
我应该带点花生的
Oh. I should've brought peanuts.
你又不能吃花生  你会过敏
You can't eat peanuts. You're allergic.
你要是死了  谁开车送我回家呢
If you die, who's going to drive me home?
我不会吃的
I'm not gonna eat them.
美国国家航空航天局的一个下属机构 负责开发与管理无人空间探测任务
这是喷气推进实验室做会的事
It's a thing they do at JPL.
美国在1960年代进行的无人太空任务  发射过9次  只成功过5次
当徘徊者号终于成功发射的那一次
When the Ranger mission finally had a successful launch,
控制中心就有花生
there were peanuts in the room.
从那时起  每次发射都会摆上花生
Ever since then, they have them at every launch.
听起来是很白痴的封建迷信
That sounds like a silly superstition.
应该说是传统
It's more of a tradition.
传统我倒是很喜欢
Oh! I do love a tradition.
下一家花生店你能不能靠边停一下
Could you pull over at the next peanut store?
没有这种店吧
I don't think that's a real thing.
脑筋怎么转不过来弯呢
Oh, don't be pedantic.
随便一家坚果店都行啊
Any nut store will do.
这附近应该没有卖花生的
I-I don't think we can get peanuts out here.
好吧  那今天就毁了
Ah, well, then this whole day's ruined.
现在想想  其实这更应该只是迷信
Now that I think about it, maybe it is more of a superstition.
那好险啊
Whew! That was close.
贝弗利  你打的是我手机  不是莱纳德的
Oh, uh, hey, Beverly, you called my phone, not Leonard's.
其实我是想和你聊聊
Actually, I was hoping to speak with you.
现在方便吗
Is this a good time?
看情况
Uh, that depends.
你那边现在几点
What time is it where you are?
下午刚过5点
Uh, just after 5:00.
西方文化认为下午5点前是工作时间  不宜饮酒
好吧  那也作数
Yeah, that counts.
有什么事
What's up?
我挺享受我们前几天的对话
Well, I enjoyed our conversation the other day,
希望能继续
and I was hoping to continue it.
真的吗
Really?
真的  你可能会感到意外
Uh, yes. You may find this surprising,
但其实我没有很多所谓的"闺蜜"
but I don't have a lot of what you would call girlfriends.
不会吧
What?
当然  我是有些女同事
Of course, there are my female colleagues,
不过她们都是弗洛伊德学派的
but, uh, they're all Freudians,
恋父情节就是由弗洛伊德所提出的
所以我能和她们抱怨的男人就只有我父亲
so the only boy that I can dish about is my father.
好吧  我随时奉陪
Uh, well, you know, I'm here for you.
你想聊什么
What do you want to talk about?
上次我们主要聊了我的生活
Well, last time, we focused on my life.
如果我们要当真正的闺蜜
If we're going to be real girlfriends,
也应该聊聊你的生活
we should talk about you as well.
如果我们要当真正的闺蜜
Well, you know, if we're gonna be real girlfriends,
就应该再找个女生加入  才能在背后说她坏话
we should get a third girl we can trash behind her back.
那我们就是阴损姐妹喵
Oh, so we'd be catty.
我喜欢
Oh, I like it.
谢尔顿的未婚妻怎么样
What about Sheldon's fiance?
她好像挺死气沉沉的
She seems a bit dour.
死气沉沉吗  毒喵啊
Ooh, dour? Meow.
好了
All right.
来吧
Here we go.
准备发射  十  九
L-minus ten, nine...
等等  你这是干什么  应该说"发射倒计时"
Wait, what are you doing? It's T-minus?
我曾是宇航员  我们的用语是"准备发射"
I was an astronaut. We used L-minus.
可这模型是土星五号
But this is a Saturn V,
当年发射这种火箭时  是说倒计时
and when they launched those, they said T-minus?
这是我的火箭  我说了算
It's my rocket! We're doing it my way.
好吧
Fine.
我并不知道你父亲当年离开的原因
I'm not saying I know why your dad left,
不过我好像有点头绪了
but I think I'm getting an idea.
准备发射
L-minus
十  九  八
ten, nine, eight,
七  六
seven, six...
因为你挺霸道的
'Cause you're kind of bossy.
五  四  三  二
...five, four, three, two,
一
one...
我记得它们能飞更高啊
I remember them going up higher.
这下好了
Well, that's perfect.
我唯一一件以为能和儿子一起做的事
I mean, the one thing I thought I could do with my son,
我都做不好
I can't even do that right.
你要是想再看一遍  我录了视频
Well, if you want to see it again, I got it on video.
用慢镜播放看起来还挺酷的
Looks pretty cool in slow motion.
谢谢你的支持
Thank you for your support.
-不客气  -我是在说反话
- You're welcome. - I was being sarcastic.
你好大的胆
How dare you!
谢尔顿  我该怎么办
Sheldon, what am I gonna do?
我哪懂该如何养育男孩子
I mean, what do I know about raising a boy?
难道你懂该如何养育女孩子吗
What do you know about raising a girl?
天啊   你说得对
Oh, my God, you're right.
我不知道你这话是不是讽刺
Well, I don't know if that was sarcasm or not.
所以  要么不客气  要么你讨厌
So, either you're welcome, or hey!
莱纳德  你不是真的从沙发那发短信
Leonard, did you really just text me from the couch
叫我给你的三明治多放点黄芥末吧
to put extra mustard on your sandwich?
我还担心你可能不会看手机呢
I was worried you might not check your e-mail.
我发誓  我会把三明治扔了
I swear to God, I will throw this out.
这条不是我发的
That one was not me.
等等  是你妈
Oh, wait, it was just your mom.
我妈给你发短信吗
My mother's texting you?
是啊  最近我们常聊天
Yeah. We've been talking a lot lately.
为什么
Why?
坏皇后跟墙上的魔镜聊腻了吗
She sick of talking to the magic mirror on the wall?
不是啦  我觉得她寂寞了
No, I think she's lonely.
她最近常找我聊
She's been reaching out.
好吧  小心点
Okay, just be careful.
你以为自己和她更亲近了
You think you're getting close to her,
殊不知下一刻  你就被写进书里
and the next thing you know, you're featured in a book
书名叫《他是故意的:  尿床的青少年养育记》
called He's Doing It On Purpose: Raising a Teenage Bed-Wetter.
不是那样的
No, it's not like that.
她最近常分享她的生活
You know, she's been opening up about her life,
而且对我的生活也给予很多支持
and she's actually been really supportive about mine.
-真的吗  -是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
我跟她说了我工作的事
I've been telling her about my job,
她说她为我感到骄傲
and she said she was proud of me.
真好
Well, that's great.
她从没说过为我感到骄傲
Never told me she was proud of me.
哪怕我有一整个月都没尿床
Even when I stayed dry for a whole month.
你不希望我和你妈做朋友吗
Do you not want me to be friends with your mom?
我们把话说清楚
Well, let's be clear.
我娶你是为了伤害她
I-I married you to hurt her.
这乐趣现在要被你毁了
You're kind of ruining it.
开心的第13个理由
Reason number 13 to feel good:
作为一次发射  很失败
as a launch, it was bad,
但作为一次爆炸  简直壮丽
but as an explosion, it was glorious.
第14个理由
Reason 14,
你十根手指都还在
you still have all your fingers,
男孩都喜欢有手指的爸爸
and boys prefer a dad with fingers.
感谢你的努力
Thanks for trying,
但你没法让我开心的
but you're not gonna be able to cheer me up.
那这招怎么样
Well, how about this, then?
别再叽叽歪歪了
You quit your whining before I give you
否则我打到你"鸡歪"  年轻人
something to cry about, young man.
什么
What?
我父亲以前常用这些话安慰我
Those are comforting words my father would often say.
有帮助吗
Did it help?
我现在是人中龙凤啊
I turned out great.
你说呢
You tell me.
我们走吧
Let's get going.
回家路上你也要这么丧吗
Are you gonna be this mopey all the way home?
我不知道  可能吧
I don't know, maybe.
那超高难度的三角函数谜题
There any chance you'd be cheered up
能让你打起精神吗
by an amazing trigonometry riddle?
你要是连这个都回答不了
Well, if you can't answer that,
那你肯定解不出这题
there's no way you're gonna get this riddle.
你觉得怎么样
Oh, hey, hey, what do you think?
虽说是男孩  但你也不用在他衣服上
Just because it's a boy, I don't think you need to
缝个生殖器图案吧
put a picture of genitals on his shirt.
那是棒球棒和两颗小棒球啦
But that's a baseball bat with two little baseballs.
现在我看出来了
Okay, and now I see it.
我能理解为什么
So, you know, I understand why
霍华德为儿子的出生而紧张
Howard is nervous about having a son,
但你是也是真的不开心吗
but are you really upset about it?
我其实还好啦
No, I'm fine.
只是我从小在兄弟堆中长大
It's just, I grew up with a bunch of brothers,
所以我觉得哈雷有个妹妹挺好的
so I thought it'd be nice for Halley to have a sister.
这个想法错了吗
Is that wrong?
当然错了
Of course it's wrong.
你又不知道这个男孩会成长为怎样的人
You don't know what this little boy's gonna be like.
也许他会粗鲁莽撞
Maybe he'll be rough and tumble,
也许他会温柔细心
or maybe he'll be sweet and sensitive,
也许他会集上述性格于一身  就像我
or maybe he'll be all those things, like me.
你粗鲁又莽撞吗
You're rough and tumble?
来试试看啊  小婊砸
You bet I am, bitch.
但我也很细心  我收回刚才的话
But I'm also sensitive and regret saying that.
-嗨  -好呀
- Hey. - Hello.
有空吗
You got a sec?
有呀  怎么了
Sure. What's up?
佩妮最近一直在和我妈聊天
Penny's been talking to my mother
就像好闺蜜一样  这让我心慌慌
like they're best friends, and it's kind of freaking me out.
好吧
Okay...
我敢肯定她俩不是好闺蜜
I'm pretty sure they're not best friends.
因为每个人只能有一个最好的闺蜜
'Cause you can only have one best friend.
佩妮名花有主了  那就是我
And Penny has that, and it's me.
是吗  那她正和你在视频吗
Oh, really? Is she FaceTiming with you right now?
因为她现在正跟我妈视频呢
Because she's FaceTiming with my mom, and believe me,
而我妈那张脸  应该让人看不下去才对
that is not a face you want to spend time with.
我最近确实挺忙的
Hmm. Well, I have been pretty busy lately.
也许是我对这段友情疏于照顾了
Maybe I've been neglecting our friendship.
佩妮知道我和我妈关系复杂
Penny knows I have a complicated relationship with my mother;
可她却毫不在意
it's like she doesn't even care.
实验室里事多繁杂
And with everything going on at the lab
加上还要计划婚礼
and planning the wedding,
我的空闲时间实在太少了
I just, I have so little free time.
佩妮不知道我妈有多会玩弄人于鼓掌之间
Penny doesn't know how manipulative my mother can be.
你知道世界上所谓的
Did you know there's such a thing as
逆反再逆反之三重逆反心理学吗
reverse, reverse, reverse psychology?
因为...  真的有
Because... there is.
她一定觉得自己受冷落了
I mean, she must feel so abandoned.
她太习惯我在她左右
She's used to me being there all the time,
但我现在有了自己的生活
but now I have my own life,
她只能自己适应这件事
and she's just gonna have to accept it.
为什么我妈为佩妮骄傲  而不是为我骄傲
And why is my mom proud of Penny and not me?
最重要的问题是  为什么佩妮不愿意
I mean, the real question is: why is Penny so afraid of me
接受我成长的事实
growing as a person?
我也有擅长的东西呀
I'm good at stuff, too!
我也值得拥有自己的生活呀
I deserve my own life!
好了  多谢
Okay, well, thanks.
聊得愉快
Good talk.
研究证明
You know, studies have shown
会受情绪影响而分心的人
that people distracted by emotional issues
都是垃圾司机
are poor drivers.
那遇到烦人乘客才分心的人呢
What about people distracted by irritating passengers?
这倒是很难去证实
That would be hard to test,
因为烦人是一种主观的素质
because irritating is a subjective quality.
强烈反对
Strongly disagree.
能让我开车吗
Can I drive?
不行
No.
你不会开车
You can't drive.
你连驾照都没有
You don't even have a license.
我其实有
Actually, I do.
真的吗  什么时候的事
Really? Since when?
3年前
Three years ago.
我有段时间迷上了考执照
I went on a bit of a license kick.
我还是个职业渔民
I'm also a commercial fisherman.
那你为什么从不自己开车
Then why don't you ever drive yourself?
老实说  我考试也是低分通过
Honestly, I barely passed my test.
而我唯一一次独自开车上路
And the one time I drove on my own,
调了个头  开始晕车  吐了满身  最后走回家
I made a U-turn, got dizzy, threw up and walked home.
你真的想开车吗
You really want to drive?
感觉是个很好的时机啊
It seems like the perfect time.
大路笔直  没有车来车往
The roads are straight, there's no one around,
你看起来也不太在乎自己的死活
and you don't seem to care if you live or die.
活着  谢尔顿  我绝对想活着
Live, Sheldon. I want to live.
这样事情就有点难度了
That makes things a little trickier,
不过我会尽力而为
but I'll do my best.
嗨  佩...
Hi, Pen...
哦  是你啊  莱纳德
Oh, hello, Leonard.
你好  妈妈  最近怎么样
Hello, Mother. How are you?
-很好  你呢  -我也不错
- Fine. And you? - I'm great.
好吧  很高兴和你聊天
Well, it's been lovely catching up.
等等  等一下  我们需要谈一谈
Wait. Hang on. We need to talk.
我的老天
Oh, brother.
我想知道  你为什么不为我骄傲
I want to know, why aren't you proud of me?
真正的问题难道不该是
Well, isn't the real question,
"你为什么不为你自己骄傲"
"Why aren't you proud of yourself?"
不  那也是一个问题  我常自问
No, that is a question-- and I ask it a lot--
不过现在还是先回答我的问题吧
but let's stick with the one I asked you.
你为什么会觉得我不为你自豪呢
But why do you think I'm not proud of you?
因为你从来没说过呀
Because you never say it.
可你和佩妮聊了两天
But two days into chatting with Penny,
你对她总是赞不绝口
and you can't stop telling her how great she is.
她的确很不错
She is great.
老实说  在我所有的儿媳和女婿中
Honestly, of all of my children's spouses,
她是我最欣赏的一个
she's the one that I'm most impressed by.
真的吗
Seriously?
真的
Yes.
她自信满满  体贴入微
She's confident, she's thoughtful,
而且从来没有抱怨过你半句
and she never complained about you once.
我知道这需要多强大的心里素质
I know what kind of strength that takes.
所以佩妮是你的最爱吗
So, Penny's your favorite?
我想她是的
I suppose she is.
你娶了个好姑娘  莱纳德  对此我为你骄傲
You married well, Leonard, and for that I am proud of you.
我...  我不知道...  该说什么了
I don't... I don't... I don't know what to say.
我也为你努力克制不哭而骄傲
I'm also proud of how hard you're trying not to cry.
谢谢
Thank you.
你想结束视频了吗
Would you like to hang up now?
好  眼泪要决堤了
Yeah, here it comes.
你的双手在10点和2点方向
Your hands are at 10:00 and 2:00.
很好  稳稳地踩住油门
Good. Steady on the gas.
不错
Okay.
现在你可以慢慢换车道了
Now you're gonna want to slowly switch lanes.
为什么呀
Why?
因为现在路上只有两条车道
Because there are only two,
而你不在任何一条上
and you're not in either of them.
做得好  完美
Attaboy. Well done!
谢谢
Thank you.
上次开车时我还吓得半死
The last time I drove, I was terrified,
今天开车可真有趣
but this is fun.
你开得很不错
You're doing great.
你也是一个好老师
You're a good teacher.
有你这样的爸爸  你儿子一定很幸运
Your son is going to be lucky to have you as a father.
谢谢你
Thanks.
你觉得我可以试着再开快一点吗
Do you think I could try going a little faster?
想做就去做吧  小冠军
Go for it, champ.
疼呀
Ow.
抱歉
Sorry.
轻轻踩一下油门  然后...
Just ease on the gas, and...
踩多了  踩多了
Oh, too much! Too much!
我之前在怕什么  这真是太刺激了
Why was I scared of this? This is exhilarating!
刺激个大头鬼  慢下来
No, it's not! Slow down!
别对我指手画脚的  你又不是我爸爸
Don't tell me what to do! You're not my father!
你知道你开得有多快吗
Do you know how fast you were going?
时速180公里
112.
把驾照给我
Let me see your license.
-听着  我的计划是...  -闭嘴
- Okay, here's the plan. -No.
好吧
Fine.
给你
There you go.
算了  这驾照你留着吧
You know what, you can just keep it.